Welcome to this short course on
LandChain for large language model application development.
By prompting an llm or large language model,
it's now possible to develop AI applications much faster than ever before.
But an application can require prompting an llm multiple times and parsing as output.
So there's a lot of glue code that needs to be written.
LandChain created by Harrison Chase makes this development process much easier.
I'm thrilled to have Harrison here,
who had built this short course in collaboration with
deeplearning.ai to teach how to use this amazing tool.
Thanks for having me. I'm really excited to be here.
LandChain started as an open source framework for building all on applications.
It came about when I was talking to a bunch of folks in the field who were
building more complex applications and saw
some common abstractions in terms of how they were being developed.
We've been really thrilled at the community adoption of LandChain so far.
So look forward to sharing it with everyone
here and look forward to seeing what people build with it.
In fact, as a sign of LandChain's momentum,
not only does it have numerous users,
but there are also many hundreds of contributors to the open source.
This has been instrumental for its rapid rate of development.
This team really shifts code and features at an amazing pace.
So hopefully, after this short course,
you'll be able to quickly put together some really cool applications using LandChain.
And who knows, maybe you even decide to
contribute back to the open source LandChain effort.
LandChain is an open source development framework for building applications.
We have two different packages,
a Python one and a JavaScript one.
They're focused on composition and modularity.
So they have a lot of individual components that can be
used in conjunction with each other or by themselves.
And so that's one of the key value adds.
And then the other key value add is a bunch of different use cases.
So chains of ways of combining these modular components into
more end-to-end applications and making it
very easy to get started with those use cases.
In this class, we'll cover the common components of LandChain.
So we'll talk about models.
We'll talk about prompts, which are how you get
models to do useful and interesting things.
We'll talk about indexes,
which are ways of ingesting data so that you can combine it with models.
And then we'll talk about chains,
which are more end-to-end use cases along with agents,
which are a very exciting type of end-to-end use case,
which uses the model as a reasoning engine.
We're also grateful to Ankush Gholar,
who is the co-founder of LandChain alongside Harrison Chase,
for also putting a lot of thoughts into
these materials and helping with the creation of this short course.
And on the deep learning.ai side,
Jeff Ludwig, Eddie Hsu, and Diala Ezzedine,
have also contributed to these materials.
And so with that, let's go on to the next video where we'll learn
about LandChain's models, prompts, and pauses.