welcome to this short course on langchain for
large language model
application development
by prompting an LLM m or large language model
is now possible
to develop
AI applications much faster than never before
but an application can require
prompting an LLM multiple times
and pausing as output
and so does a lot of glue coat that needs to be written
langchain treated by Harrison Chase
makes this development process much easier
I'm thrilled to have Harrison here
who had built this
short course in collaboration with Deep Learning AI
to teach how to use this amazing tool
thanks for having me
I'm really excited to be here
LangChain started as an open source framework
for building LLM applications
it came about when
I was talking to a bunch of folks in
the field who were building
more complex
applications and saw some comet abstractions
in terms of how they were being developed
and we've been really
thrilled at the community adoption of link chain
so far
and so look forward to sharing it with everyone here
and look forward to seeing what people build with it
in fact as a sign of langchains momentum
not only does it have numerous users
but there are also many
hundreds of contributors to the open source
and this has been instrumental for this
rapid rate of development
this team really
ships cold and features at an amazing pace
so hopefully after the short course
you'll be able to
quickly put together some really cool applications
using LangChain
and who knows
maybe
you even decide to contribute back to the open source
LangChain effort
Lang Chain is an open source
development framework for building LLM applications
we have two different packages
a Python one and a Javascript one
they are focused on composition and modularity
so they have a lot of individual components
that can be used
in conjunction with each other or by themselves
and so that's one of the key value ads
and then the other key value ad is a bunch of
different use cases
so
chains of ways of combining these modular components
into more end and applications and making it
very easy to get started
with those use cases
in this class we'll cover
the common components of langchain
so we'll talk about models
we'll talk about prompts
which are how you
get models to do useful and interesting things
we'll talk about indixes which are ways of
ingesting data so that you can combine it with models
and then we'll talk about chains
which are more end to end use cases
along with agents
which are a very exciting type of end to end use case
which uses the model as a reasoning engine
we're also grateful to Anguish Golar who is
a co founder of Lang Chain alongside Harrison Chase
for also putting a lot of thought into these materials
in hoping with the creation of this short horse
and on the deep learning the AI side
Jeff Ladwick Edishu and Tiala
Azidine have also contributed to these materials
and so with that let's go on to the next video
we will learn about lankings
models prompts and puzzles